nintendoage.com 2014-06-25

# 

**Bucket Head Media Privacy Policy**  
(Last updated $Date: 2013/03/31 16:47:35 $)

Bucket Head Media LLC ("Bucket Head") is committed to respecting the privacy of persons using www.NintendoAge.com, www.SegaAge.com, and www.PlaystationCollecting.com (the "Sites"). This Privacy Policy describes Bucket Head's information gathering and dissemination practices for the Sites. 

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully prior to using a Site. By using a Site, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

**__Collection of Personal Information__**

When you establish an account on a Site, you must provide us with certain personal information, including but not limited to as applicable your age, name and e-mail address. We may also request information about your interests and activities and other demographic information. 

Within a Site, if you interact with other Members, we may share additional information with such other Members. The additional information you share by participating in a Site is your choice and responsibility. Similarly, information you share through messaging within a Site is solely your responsibility. 

We may also collect and analyze information your use of a Site for statistical purposes. This information may be analyzed and/or aggregated to determine appropriate modifications and enhancements to a Site. 

Bucket Head may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the Sites. Your IP address may be used with the IP addresses of other members to gather broad demographic information. 

**__Cookies__**

We and/or our business partners may use "cookies" in connection with a Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site places on an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes and/or to enhance a user's experience. Through the use of cookies, we also may automatically collect information about your online activity on our site, such as the web pages you visit, the time and date of your visits, the links you click, and the searches you conduct on our Site. During your visits to other websites where we advertise, we (or third parties) may use certain data collected on our Site to show you the type of Bucket Head advertisements likely to be of greater interest to you. You may adjust your computer to disallow the storing of cookies. However, certain aspects of a Site may not function properly if cookies are disabled. We are not responsible for the use of cookies by other Web sites that are accessed through us. 

**__Log Data__**

When you visit a Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type or the web page you were visiting before you came to our Site and pages of our Site that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Site and access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of a Site, for Site technical administration, to increase our Site functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor our Site to our visitors' needs. We also use this information to verify that visitors to a Site meet the criteria required to process their requests. We do not treat Log Data as personal information or use it in association with other personal information, and we may aggregate, analyze and evaluate such information. 

**__Web Beacons__**

We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your use of a Site. We also may include web beacons in advertisements or email messages to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to customize our Sites to deliver targeted advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our online advertising, content, programming and other activities. 

**__Use and Disclosure of Information__**

We do not share your personal information with others except as indicated in this Privacy Policy or when we inform you and give you an opportunity to opt out of having your personal information shared. Bucket Head will use the personal information you provide to provide a Site, alert you of new features and enhancements, respond to your support issues, and/or notify you of upgrade opportunities, promotions, and special offers. You agree that we may communicate with you via email and similar technologies for any purpose relating to a Site. 

We may also: 

  * Disclose your personal information to companies who work for Bucket Head to provide one or more parts of a Site or that provide related administrative functions (such as support services, web analytics, and fraud detection). These third parties may have access to your personal Information; if they do, this access is only so that they may perform these tasks on our behalf and they are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
  * Release personal information and/or other information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state, federal or international laws or respond to a court order, subpoena, search warrant, or other government request.
  * Disclose personal information and/or other information about you that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our agreements, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend against any third-party claims, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of a Site, and protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Bucket Head, our users or others.

**__Children__**

Bucket Head does not knowingly allow children under the age of thirteen (13) to sign up for an account on a Site or to otherwise disclose any of their personal information to us. If you are under 13 years old, please do not use or access our Site. We do not intend to collect information about children under the age of 13. If we later obtain actual knowledge that a user is under 13 years of age, we will take steps to remove that user's information from our systems. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under 13 whom you believe has disclosed personal information to us, please contact us at webmaster@nintendoage.com so that we may delete and remove the child's information from our systems. 

**__Opt-Out__**

We provide you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving certain communications from us and our business partners, by emailing us at webmaster@nintendoage.com. In addition, all marketing e-mails from Bucket Head will provide you with the opportunity to unsubscribe from future marketing mailings. Even if you opt out of such mailings, however, we reserve the right to send you e-mail and other communications to disclose maintenance and other service-related issues. 

**__Access to Account__**

If you are a registered member of a Site, you can change your account information through the account profile feature. You may need to supply certain information so that we can try to verify that you have authority to modify this information. 

**__Third-Party Sites__**

A Site may contain links to other Internet sites. We have no responsibility for the privacy practices of other web sites, including the web sites of our advertisers or business partners. Whenever a web browser window is opened in Bucket Head that does not show a web page created by Bucket Head (noted by a Bucket Head copyright statement at the bottom of such pages), then it should be assumed that Bucket Head privacy policies do not apply. 

The fact that we may link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other websites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit. 

**__Legal Requirements; Sale of Business__**

We intend to protect your privacy to the fullest extent possible as described in this policy while also fulfilling our responsibility to uphold all applicable laws and regulations. Due to potential legal requirements and other possible circumstances, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed or accessed in ways not otherwise described in this policy. We may be compelled under law to disclose information to government or third parties under certain circumstances or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Further, we can, and you hereby authorize us to, disclose any information to law enforcement or other government officials that we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in compliance with the law. 

In the event that all or part of Bucket Head is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, you agree that we may transfer or assign the information we have collected from you as part of such merger, acquisition, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used. 

**__United States__**

A Site is hosted in the United States. If you are accessing a Site from outside the United States, please be advised that through your continued use of a Site, which is governed by U.S. law and this Privacy Policy, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer. 

**__Security Measures__**

We have implemented reasonable security measures on a Site to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the personal information under our control. Additionally, Bucket Head takes reasonable steps to ensure that our third party business partners, including our hosting partners, provide sufficient protection for personal information. However we cannot and do not guarantee absolute security. 

**__Modifications__**

This Privacy Policy may be revised periodically by Bucket Head, as reflected by the "last modified" date below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. Your continued use of a Site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions.
